### Contact

gobluegirl@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashley-reef-rn-bsn-32a61a5b (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare

Hospitals

Clinical Research

### Certifications

Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS)

Basic Life Support for Healthcare Providers (BLS)

### Honors-Awards

Summa Cum Laude

Dorothy A.P. Lunnessan Award for Excellence in the Life Sciences

# Ashley Reef RN, BSN

Nurse Coordinator - ACHD Program - Houston Methodist Houston, Texas Area

## Summary

Experienced Leader with a demonstrated history of working in the health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Customer Service, Marketing, Pediatrics, Palliative Care, and Hospice. Strong healthcare services professional with the ability to adapt to serve any patient population across the lifespan in practice environments ranging from assisted living to critical care.

## Experience

**Houston Methodist** 

Nurse Coordinator, Lead Staff RN - Adult Congenital Heart Disease Program

February 2019 - Present (1 year 5 months)

Houston, Texas

Coordination of all facets of congenital heart program including: patient and staff education, oversight of all QI projects, prioritization of patient referrals, METEOR data extraction parameter development, planning and presentation of ACHD multidisciplinary and ACHD transplant pre-MRB conferences, coordination of care for CHD patients admitted to HMH and the Methodist Health System hospitals, clinical support to two ACHD physicians

Seasons Hospice & Palliative Care Clinical Nurse Liaison - Texas Medical Center August 2018 - February 2019 (7 months) Houston, Texas

#### **OnPointe**

1 year 5 months

Infection Control Nurse April 2018 - August 2018 (5 months)

Conroe, Texas

Assistant Director Of Nursing September 2017 - August 2018 (1 year) Houston, Texas Area

Interim Director of Nursing September 2017 - February 2018 (6 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Marketing & Admissions Nurse April 2017 - September 2017 (6 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Enlivant

Care Services Manager November 2016 - March 2017 (5 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Memorial Hermann Health System PICU/CICU/NICU Travel Registered Nurse March 2016 - September 2016 (7 months) Houston, Texas Area

Children's Hospital of Philadelphia CICU/NICU/PICU Registered Nurse September 2013 - June 2016 (2 years 10 months) Philadelphia, Pennsylvania

Nemours ECMO Specialist/CICU Registered Nurse 2009 - 2013 (4 years) Wilmington, DE

Johns Hopkins Hospital Clinical Nurse Extern May 2007 - December 2008 (1 year 8 months) Baltimore, Maryland

## Education

University of Michigan
Bachelor's degree, Biopsychology · (1997 - 2001)

Neumann University

Bachelor's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2005 - 2008)

University of South Alabama

Doctor of Nursing Practice; Masters of Science, Acute Care Pediatric Nurse Practitioner with Subspecialty in Palliative Care · (2010)